&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：最后，让我们看看ToBoolean抽象操作。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And finally, let's look at the ToBoolean abstract operation.
顺便说一下，这四个就是我们现在看到的，两个原始的，两个字符串，
And by the way, these four are what we're looking at, two primitive, two string,
两个数字和两个布尔值。
two number, and two Boolean.
还有它们引用和使用的其他抽象操作。
There are other abstract operations that they refer to and use.
所以如果你好奇的话，请阅读规范中的内容，但是
So read those in the spec if you're curious, but
这些是你将要遇到的主要问题。
these are the major ones you're gonna run into.
因此ToBoolean，规范中的第7.1.2节。
So ToBoolean, section 7.1.2 in the spec.
任何时候您有任何不是布尔值的值，并且
Anytime you have any value that is not a Boolean, and
它用于需要布尔值的地方，发生此操作。
it's used in a place that needs a Boolean, this operation occurs.
和其他的一模一样，好吗？
Exactly the same as the other ones, okay?
此操作的算法较少，查找较多。
This operation is less algorithmic and more lookup.
其实没什么可做的，除了说，就是价值，
There's not really anything to do, other than to say, is the value,
我们所谓的错误，或者不是，这是这里唯一的问题。
what we call falsy, or not, that's really the only question here.
所以本质上有一个查询表。
So there's essentially a look up table.
说明书中的字面意思是，如果是这样的话，这里是其中一个东西的价值
Literally in the spec, that says, here is the value of one of these things if so
返回false，意味着false值是从ToBoolean返回的值。
return false, meaning the false value is what came back from ToBoolean.
否则只返回true。
And otherwise just return true.
因此，它定义了一个非常具体且有限的列表，我们称之为伪值。
So it defines a very specific and short limited list of what we call falsy values.
即强制为布尔值时将返回false的值，
That is values that will return false when coerced to a Boolean,
以及可以强制使用布尔值的各种方法中的任何一种。
and any of the various ways that you can coerce to a Boolean.
这些是虚假的价值观。
These are the falsy values.
空字符串，0、NULL、NaN、FALSE和
The empty string, either of the 0, the null, the NaN, the false, and
未定义的。
the undefined.
这些都是我们虚假的价值观。
Those are our falsy values.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：如果它不在那个列表上，它总是真实的，好吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: If it's not on that list, it is always truthy, okay?
如果它不在名单上，它是真实的。
If it's not on the list, it is truthy.
所以那个清单上的一些例子，那个清单是无限长的。
So some examples of things on that list, that list is infinitely long.
但有些例子是字符串，
But some examples would be a string,
数字，对象，数组，真，函数。
a number, an object, an array, true, function.
这些都是真实的价值观。
Those are all truthy values.
让我们看看你是否注意到了。
Let's see if you're paying attention.
如果你尝试两个布尔值一个空数组会发生什么？
What would happen if you try to two Boolean an empty array?
它是真实的还是虚假的？
Would it be truthy or would it be falsy?
所以请密切注意我对ToBoolean的描述，
So pay very close attention to how I describe to ToBoolean,
它不调用两个原始算法。
it does not invoke the two primitive algorithm.
或者两个数字，或者TO字符串，或者其他任何东西，它只是进行查找。
Or the two number, or the to string, or anything, it just does a look up.
那么，false上的空数组是列表吗？
So is the empty array on the falsy the list?
&gt；&gt；类：否。
&gt;&gt; class: No.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：那么它必须返回什么？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So what must it return?
&gt；&gt；类：真实。
&gt;&gt; class: Truthy.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：真的，好吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: True, okay?
当你对布尔值做的时候，这是你要记住的一件关键事情，
That's a key thing to keep in your mind when you're doing to Booleans,
当这就是正在发生的事情，就没有其他强迫的事情发生了。
when that's what's happening, there's no other coercion stuff happening.
只是直视一下，到底有没有。
It's just a straight look up, is it there or is it not.
您不能用字符串或任何值覆盖它。
You can't override it with a value over to string or anything.
只是它在名单上还是不在，好吗？
It's just is it on the list or is it not, okay?
所以这就是我们如何得到虚假和真实的价值观。
So that's how we get our falsy and truthy values.
本质上，记住列表中的错误，并且
Essentially, memorize the falsy the list, and
然后总是问列表上的值是不是假的，否则，它必须是真的。
then always ask is the value on that list if so falsy, otherwise, it must be truthy.